Guide to the Riot Grrrl zine and music collection, circa 1989-1997.
Riot Grrrl zine and music collection,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Riot Grrrl zine and music collection, circa 1989-1997.
8125
Wobensmith, Matt
2 cubic feet.
Printed materials, posters, ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
A collection of more than 250 Riot Grrrl-related zines along with original cassette tapes and seven-inch singles from Bikini Kill, Bratmobile, Skinned Teen, and others bands who pioneered the movement and its sound. Topics of the zines span across queer culture, punk rock, sexual politics, the gay skinhead movement, skate culture, feminism and gender roles, covering a wide geographical area from the late 1980s through the 1990s.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Riot grrrl is an underground feminist punk movement that originated in the early 1990s in Washington state. It is a subcultural movement that combines feminist consciousness and punk style and politics.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
A collection of more than 250 Riot Grrrl-related zines along with original cassette tapes and seven-inch singles from Bikini Kill, Bratmobile, Skinned Teen, and others bands who pioneered the movement and its sound. Topics of the zines span across queer culture, punk rock, sexual politics, the gay skinhead movement, skate culture, feminism and gender roles, covering a wide geographical area from the late 1980s through the 1990s.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wobensmith, Matt.
Subjects:
Feminism.; Gender identity.; Punk rock music.; Riot grrrl movement.; Women in popular culture.; Women rock musicians.; Women singers.; Young women.
Form and Genre Terms:
Zines.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Associated material is held in the Riot Grrrl Collection in NYU's Fales Library.
NOTES
These materials are from the personal collection of Matt Wobensmith, publisher of the zine Outpunk between 1992 and 1997, and curator of multiple exhibitions on zine culture.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Zines
Series II. Posters and Ephemera
Series III. Sound and Video Recordings
CONTAINER LIST
- Zines, 1984-2016
  Zines are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - A-E, 1987-2016
    - A Bitchin' Zine!!, Undated; Totally Radical Muslims (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Vol 1 (2 copies)
    - A Girl2, 1994; Andrea (Box 1, Folder 2)
      North Vancouver, Canada
    - A Zine About Womens Self Defense, 2006-12; Isy; Spanna; Becs (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Issue #1
      Brighton, United Kingdom
    - Ablaze!, 1987; Ablaze, Karren (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Issues #1 and 2
      Leeds, United Kingdom
    - Ablaze!, 1993; Ablaze, Karren (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Issue #10
      Huggy Bear
    - El-e-ment'al Records Presents, 1993; SR-20748; Bivouac; Trumans Water; Jacob's Mouse; Cornershop; El-e-ment'al Records; Wiiija (Box 1, Folder 5)
      7" vinyl record included with Ablaze issue #10. Contains the songs "Dragging Your Weight Around," "Soar Ossinaxx at Long Last," "Kettle," and "Change"
    - Above Lucite, 1999; Katz, Emily (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Issue #2
      Syracuse, New York
    - Adventures in Food, 1998; Tharp, Alison (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Issues #2 and 3
      Stockton, California
    - Alien, 1997; Polo, Whitney (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Issue #11
      Berkeley, California
    - Almost…, 2004; Penguin in Peril (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Amazine, 1994; Amazon Girlz (Box 1, Folder 10)
      San Jose, California
    - Amplified Heart, Undated; Zoe; Megan (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Toronto, Ontario
    - Anodyne, 1995-02; Julie (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Issue #5
      Portland, Oregon
    - Are You Ready for Hillary?, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Art Opening!, Undated; Boyer, Jody; Weber, Elka; White, Muffie (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Artbabe, 1993; Abel, Jessica (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Chicago, Illinois
    - Atta Girl, Undated; Rebecca (Box 1, Folder 16)
      San Francisco, California
    - Awkward, 1999; Schrag, Ariel; Slave Labor Graphics (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ball-Buster, 1993-1994; Amanda (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Issues #1, 2, and 3
      Columbus, Ohio
    - Benedict Gehlen, 1993-04; Gehlen, Benedict (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Olympia, Washington
    - Big Bums, 2008-08; Cooper, Charlotte; Hyatt, Kay; Murphy, Simon; Savage, Bill (Box 1, Folder 20)
      London, United Kingdom
    - Bikini Kill: A Color and Activity Book, 1990; Bikini Kill (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Early reproduction
    - Bitch Bitch Bitch, 1994; Gregory, Roberta (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Seattle, Washington
    - Bitch Queen, 1992; Michelle (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Boston, Massachusetts
    - Bitter Pie, 1999-08-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Issues #4 and 6 1/2
    - Bones to Fly. Getaway Go-Cart., Undated; D'Mere, Meadow (Folder 25)
    - Book of Sleep, 1999; Bell, Gabrielle (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Brazen Hussy Comics, Undated; Caroline (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Gainesville, Florida
    - Burning Farm, 1993-04; Jane (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Issue #4
    - Butt Ugly, 1993; V., Cory (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Issue #8
      Wankesha, Wisconsin
    - Citron Limette, 1999; Castre, Fidle (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Malahat, British Columbia, Canada
    - Color Right, Winter '95-96; Mericle, Charise; Primal Groove Press (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Comix Comix, 1996; Gregory, Roberta (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Consumer, The, Undated; Spark, Matt (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Issue #28
    - Creme Brulee, 1993-07; Johns, Abigail E. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Cupsize, 1995; Emelye; Sasha (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Issue #3
      New York, New York
    - Daughter of the Water Demon, The, Undated; Rapoport, Katya (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Death and Tortillas, 1995-1996; McWilliams, Erin (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Issues #1 and #2
      Fairview Village, Pennsylvania
    - Deep Date, Undated; S., Amy; HardKore Art Deth Publications (Box 2, Folder 3)
      HardKore Art Deth Publications Number 002
    - Definition, 1996; Schrag, Ariel (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Second edition
    - Discharge, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Issues #4 and 5
      Alexandria, Virginia
      Arlington, Virginia
    - Don't Be a Hard Rock When You Really Are a Gem, Baby Girl…, Undated; Mitchell, Kimberly (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
    - Doris, Winter 95; Crabb, Cindy (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Issues #2-5 and 8-9
      Oakland, California
      Asheville, North Carolina
    - Doris, 1998-02-2001; Crabb, Cindy (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Issues #10-11 and 13-17
    - Doris, 2001-2008; Crabb, Cindy; Microcosm Publishing (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Issues #18-26
      Athens, Ohio
    - Doris, 2012-2016; Crabb, Cindy (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Issues #29-32
    - East Village Inky, The, 2001; Halliday, Ayun (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Brooklyn, New York
    - Escape Route, 2010-03; Skate Like a Girl San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Exorcise Book, 2013; Gontijo Araujo, Rachel; Sauer, Stephanie; Benjamin, Heather; A Bolha Editora (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
    - Exploring Time and Space, 1994; K., Gregory; Nobody Photocopyations (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - F-J, 1984-2014
    - F*Zine, 2002; Tyler, Jessica; Camba, Liza F. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Irvine, California
    - Fear of Fear, 2003; Anxiety, Annie (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fem Rockers U Should Know, Undated; Miller, Barbie (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Two copies
    - Femme Flicke, 1994; Tina (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Allston, Massachusetts
    - Femzine, 1984-12; Dena (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Avengers, The
      Rubella Ballet
    - Fernzine, 1994; Fern, Kim (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Issue #6
      Normal, Illinois
    - Figments of a Diseased Imagination, Undated; Inertia, Delyreeum V. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - For the Working Girls, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Toronto, Ontario, Canada
    - Free to Choose: A Guide to Reproductive Freedom, Undated; Soutine, Jai; Eberhardt Press (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Friends of Lulu, Undated; Estrada, Jackie (Box 3, Folder 10)
      San Diego, California
    - Frontier, 2013-09; Jo, Hellen; Youth in Decline (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Function, Undated; Dawn (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Canoga Park, California
      Spitboy
    - Gaslight, 1994; Cheng, Terri Ru (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Girl Germs, 1992; Neuman, Molly; Wolfe, Allison (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Bratmobile
    - Girl Swirl Fanzine, Undated; Hipp, Taryn (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Grope, 1995; Kristen (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Arcata, California
    - Guerilla Graywater Girls Guide to Water, The, Undated; The Guerilla Graywater Girls (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - H.T.A., 1993-12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Halo, Undated; W., Chason (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Hayward, California
    - Have You Seen the Dog Lately?, Undated; Megan; Serena; Jenny (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Volume 4, Issue #1
    - Hermana, Resist, Undated; Martinez, Noemi (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Issue #1 (2 copies)
      La Blanca, Texas
    - Hey Mexican!, Undated; Ortiz, Bianca (Box 3, Folder 22)
      San Pablo, California
    - Hey There, Barbie Girl!, 1994-1995; Barbara (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Issues #2 and 4
      Ney York City, New York
    - High Drive Publications Catalog, Undated; Kelso, Megan; High Drive Publications (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - High School Hell, 1998; Tara; Lyndsay; Nicole (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - High St. Este de Oakland Tierra De Lucha y Limones, 2012-12; Montano, Brenda (Box 3, Folder 26)
      3 copies
    - Hope, 2002-03; Nelson, Elissa (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Issue #19
    - Hot Girls, 2014; Nyegaard, Chelsea (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Vol 1
      New Orleans, Louisiana
    - Hot Lava Monster, 1992-06; Jennifer (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Daly City, California
    - Hothead Paisan: Homicidal Lesbian Terrorist, 1994; DiMassa, Dianne (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Issue #15
      New Haven, Connecticut
    - Huggy Nation, Undated; Huggy Bear (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - I (Heart) Me, 1993; Taylor, Val (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - I Spy…, 2002; Loff, Christina; Sellers, Chris (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - I'm So Fucking Beautiful, Undated; Lamm, Nomy (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Indulgence, 2002; Whitney, Eleanor (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Infested with Midgets, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Boulder, Colorado
    - Ink Geek Comics, 1993-11-19; Tomine, Adrian; Bordeaux, Ariel (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Inkling, 2003-10; Klein, Melissa (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Introducing… The Fat Femme Mafia, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Is This Logical Evolution or a Zone of Illusion?", Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Jank, Summer 1994; Janelle; Jeff (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Issues #11 and 13-14
    - Jezebel, Undated; Cat, Ane (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Richmond, Victoria, Australia
    - John Doe, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      McKinleyville, California
  - K-P, 1991-2013
    - K-9 in Girl Gang, 1998; K-9; Fly (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Karbala: Fired Resistance Stories, 2013; Totally Radical Muslims (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Issue #2 (2 copies)
    - Kingfish, 1993; Sam (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Issue #2-3
    - Kitten Kore, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Los Angeles, California
    - Kurt Cobain Was Lactose Intolerant Conspiracy Zine, 1998-05-07; Callis, Kelli (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Lady Fest, 2000; Koetje, Marie (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Life and Times of Butch Dykes, The, 2009-2014; B and D Press (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Issue #1 Vol 1, Issue #2 Vol 1, Issue #3 Vol 1, Issue #2 Vol 2, Issue #1 Vol 3, Issue #2 Vol 3, Issue #1, Vol 4, Issue #1 Vol 5, Issue #1 Vol 6
    - Little Sister's Obzine, 1993; Wellings, Paula; Lowe, Lisa; Braude, Allen; Fuller, Janine (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada
    - Lonewolf, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      On verso of Love Trinkets zine
      Jackson, Wisconsin
    - Longest Spoon, The, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Love Trinkets, 1994-07-07 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      On verso of Lonewolf zine
      Omaha, Nebraska
      Madiscon, Wisconsin
    - Mad Planet, 1993; Dyer, Sarah (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Issue #3 (2 copies)
      Staten Island, New York
    - MadWoman, 1995-06; Perkins, Helena (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Issue #7
      Champaign, Illinois
    - Make-Out Session, Undated; Julie (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Atlanta, Georgia
    - Mamasita!, Undated; Bianca (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Issues #1 and 3
    - Marks in Time: The Very Early Go-Go's, 1992-02; Eden; Iraya (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Go-Go's, The
    - Mary Vulture, 1992; Kebrina (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Eureka, California
    - Menstrual, 1994-05; Spector, Shira (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Milepost One Eleven, 1998; Lynn, Barrie; Balawejder, Alani; Buttwig Productions (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Aptos, California
    - Montgomery, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Ottawa, Ontario, Canada
    - More Than a Feeling, 2001; Bridie (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - More Than Music, Summer 2001; More than Music Fest Collective (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. Wurm's house, 1998-06-02; Lake, Meghan; White, Muffie; Dawn, Cleo (Box 5, Folder 6)
      North Kingstown, Rhode Island
      Edmonton, Alberta, Canada
    - Mucus de Puce, 1998; Castre, Fidle (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Mudflap, 1991-1992; Greta (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Issue #2, 4, and 5
    - Mudflaps, 1993; Noinnud, Nytsirk (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Issue #1, Second printing
    - Mute, Undated; Gina (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - My Letter to the World, 1993; Lilly (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Rancid
      J Church
    - My Morning Feet, 1993-06; Weinman, Paul; afungusboy; Afungusboy Press (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - My New Gun, 1996-1997; White, Muffie (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Issues #2-6
      APO, AE
    - My Zine, Undated; Lamm, Rose (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Nation 1.2.3., Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Nerdy Grrrl Revolution, The, Undated; Lamm, Nomy; Taylor, Val (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Neurotic Girl and Friends, Undated; Biebrich, Tamara Rae; Szmigelski, Shannon (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada
    - New Forwarding Address, 2006-06; Niku (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Nightmare Girl, 1996-04; Lewis, Painter (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Issue #1, 4th printing
    - Noisemaker, 1994-01; Myre, Ellen (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Minneapolis, Minnesota
    - Nuthin' Good Ever Happens at 4 A.M., 2012-2013; Jetter, Avy; Stormone Originals (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Issues #1-2
    - Off My Jammy, 1998; K., Lisa (Box 5, Folder 22)
      West Somerville, Massachusetts
      Ben Folds Five
      Green Day
      Tribe 8
      Union 13
    - On Our Butts, 1994; Gamboa, Gabrielle; Gehweiler, Fawn; Aeon (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Once Were Warriors, Undated; McMillian, Jen (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Denver, Colorado
    - Oooh... Egyptian Lust Perfume!, 1998; Allen, Kalah (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Our Hero, Undated; Kale (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Canada
    - Oya, 1993-1995; La Sirne (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Issues #1, 3-7, 9-12, and 16
      Leucadia, California
    - Painter Lewis, 1996; Sts (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Parlez-Vous Code Fucker, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Pawholes, 1992; Keren; Deborah (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
    - Planet 501c3: The Next Generation, 2003; Engelberg, Miriam; CompassPoint Nonprofit Services (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Planet Girl, 1994; Martinez, Jennifer (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Plume, 1993; Sheila (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Scarsdale, New York
      Superchunk
      Tiger Trap
    - Prone to Fall, Undated; Hopeless, Heather (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Goleta, California
    - Pulp, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Pure Tuna Fish, 1996; Rita Fatila (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Issue #5-6
      St. Thomas, Ontario, Canada
  - Q-Z, 1989-2014
    - Quickie: Bond Baggage, 1997; O'Steen, Ursula (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Rebel Grrrl, Winter 2001-2002; Emelda; Sophie Magone; Julie (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Santa Cruz, California
    - Red Hanky Panky, 1996; House, Rachael (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Red Hot Mama, 1998; S., Suzanne; G., Deborah (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Long Beach, California
    - Reggae Chicken, 1993; Huggy Bear (Box 6, Folder 9)
      United Kingdom
    - Riot Grrrl, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Riot Grrrl!, Fall/Winter 1998; Wilson, Jessica; Gallahorn, Jen; Katsikas, Colette; Magruder, Jenna; Smith, Sara; Rooks, Margaret; Allie; Devosby, Jen; Suzanne (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Issues #2-3
      Northampton, Massachusetts
      Amherst, Massachusetts
      South Hadley, Massachusetts
    - Riot Grrrl Review!, Winter 1996/Spring 1997; Kristy (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Fort Myers, Florida
    - Rutabaga Zine, 1991-1992; Rzl; Bitz (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Sand Box Brats, Undated; Dull; Kelley; Josh; Kris (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Binghamton, New York
    - Secret Nicole, Undated; Martensen, Nicole; Millett, Amanda (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Issue #1, Volume 1
    - Septophilia Mail-Order, Undated; Sarah; Jen (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Iowa City, Iowa
    - Servings, 2005-08 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - SF Bay Area Girl Convention Infozine, The, 1997; Gina; Stephanie (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Sinester Cherry, Undated; Ortiz, Bianca (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Skunk, 1994; Margaret; Wish, Steve; Girl-Trouble Publications (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Slightly More Than Sound Bytes, 2004; Carfagnini, Jess (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Slow Poke Comix, 1998-11; Sorensen, Jen; Alternative Comics (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Slumber Party Games, Undated; Whitknee; Basil; Marie (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Downers Grove, Illinois
      Kalamazoo, MI
      Pacific Palisades, CA
    - Sour Mash, 1992-08; Rzl (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Sister Spit, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Spin=0, 1993-06; Reed, Jenna; Pond, Lucien; Swan; Hangnail Press (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Book One, Third printing
    - Spitboy Rule: Tales of a Female Punk Band, The, 2014; Gonzales, Michelle (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Revised edition (3 copies)
    - Spun, Undated; O., Lisa (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Suburbia, Undated; Moss, Cecilia (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Issues #1 and 3-4
      Point Richmond, California
    - Super Dork, Undated; Marlene (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Swiss Army Butt, 1994; Keara (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Oxford, Ohio
    - Tact?, 1995; P.L.M (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Tales from the Dike Side, 1996-09; Reeve, E.; Hell Cat Comix (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Montreal, Quebec, Canada
    - Tantrum Comics Preview, 2001; Engelberg, Miriam (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Teenage Gang Debs, Late Summer 2004; Smith, Erin; Smith, Don (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Issues #2-5
      Bethesda, Maryland
      Red Kross
      Lunachicks, The
      Nation of Ulysses, The
    - That Girl, 1993-2014; Callis, Kelli (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Issues #1, 5, 13 (2 copies), and 14 (2 copies)
      Valencia, California
    - That Girl, 2014; Callis, Kelli (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Issue #15 (2 copies)
    - Three A.M., 2001; Lisa, Mancini (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Issue #6-7
    - Treasure Trove, 1997; Sollberger, Eva M. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Twenty Bus, 1998; Callis, Kelli (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ugly Mug, Summer 1998; Rachelle (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Untitled, 2004; Justin, Susan (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Untitled, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Unmentionable, 1991-07; Kelina (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Issue #13
    - Urban Hipster Promo Booklet, 1998; Greg Stump; David Lasky (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Vampire Space, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Verboslammed, 1996-01; Rebecca (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Verved, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Victorie Outreach, 1997; Bright, Juliana (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Voltairine de Cleyre on Marriage, 1995; De Cleyre, Voltairine; Monkeywrench Press; The Workers Self-Education Foundation of the Industrial Workers of the World Philadelphia (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Watch Out Because Next Time You Yell Hey Babe You Might Be Left Wondering What Hit You, 2012-06; Reynold, Callie; Collective of Geniuses; Riot Grrrl Omaha (Box 7, Folder 20)
      2 copies
    - Way Down Low, 1997-1998; Sts (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - What Are U Dealing With?, Undated; Lapaolo, Angelina; Pink Taxi Productions (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Wild Honey Pie, 1995; Chan, Kristy (Box 7, Folder 23)
      Cape Coral, Florida
      Subhumans, The
      Pietasters, The
      Unrest
    - William Wants A Doll, 1994; G., Arielle (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Long Island City, New York
    - Women's How to Guide to All Sorts of Survival Skills that Help Women Take Control of Their Lives, Undated; Do-It-Herself Collective (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Volume 1
    - Women's Self-Defense, 2002; Clemenzi, Ariel (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - World Demands Revision, The, 1999-05; Waynes, Ariana; Fyrefly Press (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - World of Dorian, The, Undated; TM (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Wrong, 1997-1998; O'Steen, Ursula; Worst Impulse Press (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Xicanistas and Punkeristas Say It Loud!, Undated; Sing Your Life Lit Projects (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - XXX $*Posed, Undated; Von Mercury, Minnie; Lust Lady SF (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Yard Wide Yarns, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Donnas, The
    - 6 Volt, 1997; Taura (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Lincoln, Nebraska
- Posters and Ephemera, 1994-2010
  - Events, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Includes flyers and announcements for various conferences, festivals, and tours.
  - Promotional Materials, 1994-2010; Kill Rock Stars; Skate Like a Girl San Francisco; Action Girl (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Includes promotional materials for various organizations, record labels, and zines.
  - Miscellaneous Handbills, 1996; July, Miranda; Magnone, Sophia B.; Spitboy (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Includes a Spitboy lyric sheet, a photocopied page titled "How to Hop a Freight Train," and instructions for a video chainletter project called "Big Miss Moviola."
    Michigan
  - Villa Villa Kula Records, Undated (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Sleater Kinney
    Tattle Tale
    Kaia
    Un Cuerpo Exqui
    Ruby Falls
    Bonfire
    Madigan
    Victory at Sea
  - Heavens to Betsy "Calculated", 1994; Kill Rock Stars; John Kenny (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Heavens to Betsy
  - Yoyo A-Gogo, Summer 1998; Yoyo Recordings; Won Yu, Tae (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Cub
    Unwound
    Slant 6
    godheadSilo
    Antioch Arrow
    Karp
    Sailor
    Kicking Giant
    Yo La Tengo
    Codeine
    Neutral Milk Hotel
    Dahlia Seed
    Excuse 17
    Built to Spill
    Team Dresch
    Beck
- Sound and Video Recordings, 1991-2000
  Sound recordings are arranged alphabetically by artist name.
  - Vinyl Records, 1991-1994; 7" vinyl
    - Buildings Are the Purtiest Trees I've Seen, 1993; SR-20743; Gr'ups, The; Duotone Records (Box 8)
    - My Secret/Cool Schmool, 1992; SR-20744; Heavens to Betsy; Bratmobile; K (Box 8)
      Punk 1
    - Father, 1993; SR-20745; Lucy Stoners; Harp Records (Box 8)
      Harp #012
    - Pimp Slap, 1994; SR-20746; Glitter Roar Records (Box 8)
      Glitter Roar Records No. 1
    - Karate Hairdresser, 1993; SR-20747; Skinned Teen; Soul Static Sound (Box 8)
      Soul 1
  - Cassettes, 1991-2000
    - Athena Starwoman, 1996; TR-15917; Fat Ass Records (Box 9)
      Bennington, Vermont
    - Dreamy, 1991; TR-15918; Beat Happening; Sub Pop (Box 9)
      sp98a
    - Jamboree, 1992; TR-15919; Beat Happening; Sub Pop (Box 9)
      sp62a
    - Revolution Girl Style Now, 1991; TR-15920; Bikini Kill (Box 9)
    - There's a Dyke in the Pit, 1992; TR-15921; Bikini Kill; Tribe 8; Lucy Stoners; 7 Year Bitch; Outpunk (Box 9)
      OUT 5CA
    - Gidget Was a Minor Threat…, 1992-06; TR-15922; Bratmobile (Box 9)
    - Pottymouth, 1993; TR-15923; Bratmobile; Kill Rock Stars (Box 9)
      krs208
    - CheeseCake, 1992; TR-15924 (Box 9)
    - Scrut, 1992-06; TR-15925; Cockpit (Box 9)
    - Hand Made Luck, 1996; TR-15926; Dougher, Sarah (Box 9)
    - Plug Me In, 1998; TR-15927; Electrolettes, The; Decomposition (Box 9)
      Decomposition 04
    - Excuse Seventeen, 1993; TR-15928 (Box 9)
    - Firesign, 1998; TR-15929 (Box 9)
      Simi Valley, California
    - Flying Tigers, 1996; TR-15930 (Box 9)
    - Lightmatch Sparkalife, Undated; TR-15931; Fox, Sue P.; Kill Rock Stars (Box 9)